namaste everyone i hope all of you are
doing well
in this video we are going to look at
icici lombard
general insurance company
for intraday trading on the daily chart
the stock is in downtrend the recovery
shaped up from the support level of
1200 rupees followed by
a formation of
a double top pattern
which is in itself a bearish reversal
pattern so as you can see price
came down heavily
and this is where
it reached at 1280.
we have this
extremely long bearish candle
and these are sandwiched bullish candles
which means
buyers try to push the price higher but
because of lack of strength they could
not do it so
so if
the stock price goes any lower than
1270 rupees
we
might very well see
the support level of
1200 rupees getting challenged